mummycooks.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy & Cookie Policy – Mummy Cooks

**Privacy and Cookie Policy  **

 Collection of Information from website visitors, Mummy Cooks is committed to protecting your privacy. We have taken all the essential measures to make sure that any information you give us, remains private and secure and that your payment and registration information is processed with total confidentiality. As required by the European Data Protection laws, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information, which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. 

 We may collect the following personal data about you: 

 • your name, child’s age and sex; 

 • your postal addresses, phone (including mobile phone) and e-mail details; 

 • your browsing and online shopping activities; 

 • your date of birth; and 

 • any other information you provide to us through the website. 

 **  Cookies **

 We may use internet cookies and other types of clickstream data on visitors' hard drives. Internet cookies save, among other things, the visitor's name,screen preferences, the pages of the website viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. Internet cookies are stored on the visitor's hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by us. Visitors may decline the internet cookies by using the appropriate feature of their web browser, if available. 

 **  Use and disclosure of Personal Information**

Personal data, including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address and telephone number ("Personal Information"), that is collected by us will not be shared with third parties in a personally-identifiable form but may be used by us for purposes including, but not limited to, to protect our rights, property or to enforce the terms and conditions of this website, to comply with laws, regulations, court orders or other legal processes, to contact you or otherwise respond to your request/enquiries, for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of user behaviour, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customise content and layout of our website. In addition, Personal Information collected may be added to our databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding website updates, new products and services and other announcements. We may transfer your Personal Information to the subsidiaries, divisions, affiliates or other entities under common ownership with us. We will not sell, exchange or publish your Personal Information without your permission, except as noted above or in conjunction with a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, acquisition, or other similar event. You also agree that we may share your Personal Information with others who help us with these activities. 

 **  Use and disclosure of Anonymous Information**

 All information that is not personal to you or someone else, including, but not limited to, questions, comments, ideas and suggestions ("Anonymous Information") shall be deemed non-confidential information and owned by us. We will not obtain your consent before posting collected data on our website, or sharing it.
